Arne Oldberg Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-78, 81-85)
  - "June," rhapsody, op. 36, Photocopies of holograph harp and piano parts (Box-folder 15/12)
  - "June," rhapsody, op. 36, Photocopy of holograph full score; p. 85-133 (one of two) (Box-folder 16/1)
  - "June," rhapsody, op. 36, Photocopy of holograph full score; p. 85-133 (two of two) (Box-folder 16/2)
  - "June," rhapsody, op. 36, Transparencies of holograph full score; p. 85-133 (Box-folder 16/3)
  - A legend, holograph full score see ML96.O53 (Case)
  - A legend, Photocopy of holograph full score; 43 p. (Box-folder 17/1)
  - A legend, Holograph full score; 45 p. (Box-folder 17/2)
  - A legend, Transparencies of holograph full score; 43 p. (Box-folder 17/3)
  - A legend, Transparencies of holograph parts (Box-folder 17/4)
  - A legend, Copyist's string parts (Box-folder 17/5)
  - A legend, Copyist's woodwind parts (Box-folder 17/6)
  - A legend, Copyist's brass and percussion parts (Box-folder 17/7)
  - Pandora; cantata for soprano, tenor, baritone, mixed chorus, and orchestra, Holograph choral score; 168 p. and Photocopy of libretto typescript; 20 p. (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Pandora; cantata for soprano, tenor, baritone, mixed chorus and orchestra, Holograph full score; 469 p. and Photocopy of libretto typescript; 20 p.; Contains two pages of sketches at end. (Box-folder 19/2)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Autograph full score; 106 p. (Box-folder 20/1)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Holograph full score; 45 p. (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Printed copy, annotations in red and blue pencil; 77 p.; New York: G. Schirmer Inc., 1916.; Marked "personal copy." (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Printed copy, Oldberg's annotations in black ink and red and blue pencil; 77 p.; New York: G. Schirmer Inc., 1916.; Page three signed by Oldberg. (Box-folder 20/4)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Printed copy, annotations in black pen; 77 p.; New York: G. Schirmer Inc., 1916. (Box-folder 20/5)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Printed copy; 77 p. [one of two]; New York: G. Schirmer Inc., 1916. (Box-folder 20/6)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Printed copy; 77 p. [two of two]; New York: G. Schirmer Inc., 1916. (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Holograph trombone, tuba, and percussion parts (Box-folder 21/1)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Photocopies of holograph percussion parts (Box-folder 21/2)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Photocopies of holograph percussion, organ, and celesta parts (Box-folder 21/3)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Violin and viola parts; New York: G. Schirmer Inc., 1917. (Box-folder 21/4)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Cello and bass parts; New York: G. Schirmer Inc., 1917. (Box-folder 21/5)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Flute, oboe, and English horn parts; New York: G. Schirmer Inc., 1917. (Box-folder 21/6)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Clarinet and bassoon parts; New York: G. Schirmer Inc., 1917. (Box-folder 21/7)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Horn and trumpet parts; New York: G. Schirmer Inc., 1917. (Box-folder 21/8)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Trombone and tuba parts; New York: G. Schirmer Inc., 1917. (Box-folder 21/9)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Timpani, triangle, and harp; New York: G. Schirmer Inc., 1917. (Box-folder 21/10)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Copyist's violin parts (Box-folder 22/1)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Copyist's viola, cello, and bass parts (Box-folder 22/2)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Copyist's flute parts (Box-folder 22/3)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Copyist's oboe and English horn parts (Box-folder 22/4)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Copyist's clarinet and bassoon parts (Box-folder 22/5)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Copyist's horn parts (Box-folder 22/6)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Copyist's trumpet parts (Box-folder 22/7)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Copyist's trombone and tuba parts (Box-folder 22/8)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Autograph percussion and harp parts (Box-folder 22/9)
  - Paolo and Francesca; dramatic overture for orchestra, op. 21, Holograph organ and autograph celesta parts (Box-folder 22/10)
  - Quartet, 2 violins, viola, and cello, C minor, Holograph full score; 19 p. (Box-folder 23/1)
  - Quartet, 2 violins, viola, and cello, C major, Holograph full score in ink, with annotations in pencil; 38 p. (Box-folder 23/2)
  - Quartet, 2 violins, viola, and cello, C minor, Holograph full score in ink, with annotations in pencil; 49 p. (Box-folder 23/2)
  - Quartet, 2 violins, viola, and cello, no. 2, D major, Andante movement, Holograph sketch score in pencil; 26 p. (Box-folder 23/2)
  - Quartet, 2 violins, viola, and cello, C major, Holograph parts (Box-folder 23/3)
  - Quartet, 2 violins, viola, and cello, op. 15, C minor, Autograph first violin part (Box-folder 23/4)
  - Quartet, 2 violins, viola, and cello, op. 15, C minor, Autograph second violin part (Box-folder 23/5)
  - Quartet, 2 violins, viola, and cello, op. 15, C minor, Autograph viola part (Box-folder 23/6)
  - Quartet, 2 violins, viola, and cello, op. 15, C minor, Autograph cello part (Box-folder 23/7)
  - Quartet, 2 violins, viola, and cello, no. 2, D major, Holograph full score; 61 p. (Box-folder 23/8)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, and piano, no. 1, op. 16, B minor, Holograph full score in black ink, with annotations in blue pencil, inserts; 87 p. (Box-folder 24/1)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, and piano, no. 1, op. 16, B minor, Autograph violin II, viola, and cello parts (Box-folder 24/2)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, and piano, no. 1, op. 16, B minor, Copyist's violin parts (Box-folder 24/3)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, and piano, no. 1, op. 16, B minor, Copyist's viola and cello parts (Box-folder 24/4)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, and piano, no. 2, B minor, Photocopy of holograph full score, signed in black ink by Oldberg; 87 p. [one of two] (Box-folder 24/5)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, and piano, no. 2, B minor, Photocopy of holograph full score, signed in black ink by Oldberg; 87 p. [two of two (Box-folder 24/6)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, and piano, no. 2, B minor, Photocopy of holograph full score, with annotations in pencil and red pencil; 87 p. (Box-folder 25/1)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, and piano, no. 2, B minor, Photocopy of holograph full score, with annotations in pencil; 87 p. (Box-folder 25/2)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, and piano, no. 2, B minor, Transparencies of holograph full score, movement IV; pp. 63-87 (Box-folder 25/3)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, and piano, no. 2, B minor, Transparencies of holograph parts (Box-folder 25/4)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, and piano, no. 2, B minor, Photocopies of holograph violin parts (Box-folder 25/5)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, and piano, no. 2, B minor, Photocopies of holograph viola and cello parts (Box-folder 25/6)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, piano, op. 24, C# minor, Full score and string parts; 43 p.; Chicago: Clayton F. Summy Co., 1908 (Box-folder 26/1)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, piano, op. 24, C# minor, Violin I, viola, and cello parts; Chicago: Clayton F. Summy Co., 1908 (Box-folder 26/2)
  - Quintet, 2 violins, viola, cello, piano, op. 24, C# minor, Holograph violin II part (Box-folder 26/3)
  - Rhapsody for orchestra, no. 2, Copyist's piano part (Box-folder 26/4)
  - The sea, fantasy for orchestra, op. 47, Holograph full score in black ink, with annotations in red and blue pencil; 79 p. (Box-folder 28/1)
  - The sea, fantasy for orchestra, op. 47, Photocopy of holograph full score; 79 p. and 1 p. of text [one of two] (Box-folder 85/3)
  - The sea, fantasy for orchestra, op. 47, Photocopy of holograph full score; 79 p. and 1 p. of text [two of two] (Box-folder 85/4)
  - The sea, fantasy for orchestra, op. 47, Transparencies of holograph full score; 79 p. and 1 p. of text (Box-folder 85/5)
  - The sea, fantasy for orchestra, op. 47, Transparencies of holograph two piano score; 35 p. (Box-folder 28/2)
  - The sea, fantasy for orchestra, op. 47, Holograph flute, piccolo, oboe, and English horn parts (Box-folder 28/3)
  - The sea, fantasy for orchestra, op. 47, Holograph clarinet and bassoon parts (Box-folder 28/4)
  - The sea, fantasy for orchestra, op. 47, Holograph horn and trumpet parts (Box-folder 28/5)
  - The sea, fantasy for orchestra, op. 47, Holograph trombone and tuba parts (Box-folder 28/6)
  - The sea, fantasy for orchestra, op. 47, Holograph percussion and harp parts (Box-folder 28/7)
  - The sea, fantasy for orchestra, op. 47, Holograph bass part in black ink (Box-folder 28/8)
  - The sea, fantasy for orchestra, op. 47, Photocopies of holograph violin parts (Box-folder 28/9)
  - The sea, fantasy for orchestra, op. 47, Photocopies of holograph viola, cello, and bass parts (Box-folder 28/10)
  - Serenade pastorale, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, and piano, op. 18, Photocopy of holograph full score; 52 p. [one of two] (Box-folder 29/1)
  - Serenade pastorale, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, and piano, op. 18, Photocopy of holograph full score; 52 p. [two of two] (Box-folder 29/2)
  - Serenade pastorale, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, and piano, op. 18, Holograph full score in black ink; 66 p.; Includes Northwestern University School of Music programs. (Box-folder 29/3)
  - Serenade pastorale, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, and piano, op. 18, Transparencies of holograph full score; p. 2-52 (Box-folder 29/4)
  - Serenade pastorale, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, and piano, op. 18, Holograph piano part in black ink; 20 p. (Box-folder 29/5)
  - Serenade pastorale, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, and piano, op. 18, Holograph flute part (Box-folder 29/6)
  - Serenade pastorale, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, and piano, op. 18, Holograph oboe part (Box-folder 29/7)
  - Serenade pastorale, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, and piano, op. 18, Holograph clarinet part (Box-folder 29/8)
  - Serenade pastorale, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, and piano, op. 18, Holograph bassoon part (Box-folder 29/9)
  - Serenade pastorale, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, and piano, op. 18, Holograph horn part (Box-folder 29/10)
  - Sextet, string quartet, horn, and piano, B minor, Photocopy of holograph full score, with annotations in pencil, and pasteovers; 62 p. (Box-folder 26/5)
  - Sextet, string quartet, horn, and piano, B minor, Holograph two piano score; 64 p. (Box-folder 26/6)
  - Sextet, string quartet, horn, and piano, B minor, Transparencies of holograph string and horn parts (Box-folder 26/7)
  - Sextet, string quartet, horn, and piano, B minor, Transparencies of holograph full score; 103 p. (Box-folder 26/8)
  - Sextet, string quartet, horn, and piano, B minor, Photocopies of holograph violin and viola parts (Box-folder 27/1)
  - Sextet, string quartet, horn, and piano, B minor, Photocopies of holograph cello and horn parts (Box-folder 27/2)
  - Sinfonia, G minor, Transparencies of holograph full score; 91 p. (Box-folder 31/4)
  - Sinfonia, G minor, Holograph full score; 75 p. (Box-folder 84/3)
  - Sinfonia, G minor, Holograph violin parts (Box-folder 31/5)
  - Sinfonia, G minor, Holograph viola, cello and bass parts (Box-folder 31/6)
  - Sinfonia, G minor, Holograph flute and oboe parts (Box-folder 31/7)
  - Sinfonia, G minor, Holograph clarinet and bassoon parts (Box-folder 31/8)
  - Sinfonia, G minor, Holograph horn parts (Box-folder 31/9)
  - Sinfonia, G minor, Holograph trumpet, trombone, tuba, percussion, and harp parts (Box-folder 31/10)
  - Sinfonia, G minor, Transparencies of holograph string and percussion parts (Box-folder 31/11)
  - Sinfonia, op. 48, Photocopy of holograph full score; 76 p. [one of two] (Box-folder 32/1)
  - Sinfonia, op. 48, Photocopy of holograph full score; 76 p. [two of two] (Box-folder 32/2)
  - Sinfonia, op. 48, Holograph full score in black ink, annotations in pencil; 127 p. (Box-folder 32/3)
  - Sinfonia, op. 48, Transparencies of holograph full score; 76 p. (Box-folder 32/4)
  - Sinfonia, op. 48, Transparencies of holograph string parts (Box-folder 32/5)
  - Sinfonia, op. 48, Transparencies of holograph woodwind parts (Box-folder 33/1)
  - Sinfonia, op. 48, Holograph brass, percussion, and harp parts (Box-folder 33/2)
  - Sinfonia, op. 48, Photocopies of holograph violin parts (Box-folder 33/3)
  - Sinfonia, op. 48, Photocopies of holograph viola, cello, and bass parts (Box-folder 33/4)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Holograph piano score in black ink, with annotations in pencil; 30 p. (Box-folder 34/1)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Photocopy of holograph full score, with annotations in blue and red pencil; 49 p. (Box-folder 34/2)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Photocopy of holograph full score; 49 p. (Box-folder 34/3)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Photocopy of holograph full score; 49 p. (Box-folder 34/4)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Transparencies of holograph full score; 49 p. (Box-folder 34/5)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Transparencies of holograph string parts (Box-folder 34/6)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Transparencies of holograph woodwind, brass, and percussion parts (Box-folder 34/7)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Holograph violin I, flute I and II, oboe, clarinet, horn I and II, trumpet I and II, timpani, and triangle parts (Box-folder 34/8)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Photocopies of holograph violin parts (Box-folder 34/9)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Photocopies of holograph viola part (Box-folder 34/10)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Photocopies of holograph cello and bass parts (Box-folder 35/1)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Photocopies of holograph flute and oboe parts (Box-folder 35/2)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Photocopies of holograph clarinet and bassoon parts (Box-folder 35/3)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Photocopies of holograph horn parts (Box-folder 35/4)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Photocopies of holograph trumpet and trombone parts (Box-folder 35/5)
  - Sinfonietta, no. 6, G major, Photocopies of holograph tuba, percussion, and harp parts (Box-folder 35/6)
  - Six variations for orchestra, op. 49, Photocopy of holograph full score; 69 p. [one of two] (Box-folder 30/1)
  - Six variations for orchestra, op. 49, Photocopy of holograph full score; 69 p. [two of two] (Box-folder 30/2)
  - Six variations for orchestra, op. 49, Transparencies of holograph full score; 69 p. (Box-folder 30/3)
  - Six variations for orchestra, op. 49, Transparencies of holograph woodwind, brass, and percussion parts (Box-folder 30/4)
  - Six variations for orchestra, op. 49, Photocopies of holograph woodwind parts (Box-folder 30/5)
  - Six variations for orchestra, op. 49, Photocopies of holograph brass and percussion parts (Box-folder 30/6)
  - Six variations for orchestra, op. 49, Transparencies of holograph full score (strings only); p. 2-17 (Box-folder 84/4)
  - Six variations for orchestra, op. 49, Photocopy of holograph full score (strings only); p. 2-17 (three copies) (Box-folder 84/5)
  - Six variations for orchestra, op. 49, Transparencies of holograph string parts (Box-folder 30/7)
  - Six variations for orchestra, op. 49, Photocopies of holograph violin parts (Box-folder 30/8)
  - Six variations for orchestra, op. 49, Photocopies of holograph violin parts (Box-folder 30/9)
  - Six variations for orchestra, op. 49, Photocopies of holograph viola, cello, and bass parts (Box-folder 31/1)
  - Six variations for orchestra, op. 49, Photocopies of holograph viola parts (Box-folder 31/2)
  - Six variations for orchestra, op. 49, Photocopies of holograph cello and bass parts (Box-folder 31/3)
  - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra, Holograph piano score; p. 2-31 (Box-folder 17/8)
  - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra, Photocopy of holograph full score; 53 p. (Box-folder 85/2)
  - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra, Holograph piano score; 40 p. (Box-folder 17/9)
  - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra, Photocopy of holograph piano score; p. 2-29 (Box-folder 17/10)
  - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra, Transparencies of holograph piano score; p. 2-29 (Box-folder 17/11)
  - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra, Transparencies of holograph solo horn and string parts (Box-folder 17/12)
  - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra, Holograph string parts (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra, Holograph flute and oboe parts (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra, Holograph clarinet and bassoon parts (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra, Holograph horn parts (Box-folder 18/4)
  - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra, Holograph harp parts and one copyist's manuscript (Box-folder 18/5)
  - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra, Photocopies of holograph solo horn part (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra, Photocopies of holograph violin part (Box-folder 18/7)
  - Le son du cor for horn and orchestra, Photocopies of holograph viola, cello, and bass parts (Box-folder 18/8)
  - Sonata, cello and piano, op. 45 see also Sonata, viola and piano, op. 45b, B-flat minor, Holograph cello parts (Box-folder 27/3)
  - Sonata, cello and piano, op. 45, Transparencies of holograph full score; 35 p. (Box-folder 27/4)
  - Sonata, cello and piano, op. 45, Transparencies of holograph cello part (Box-folder 27/5)
  - Sonata, cello and piano, op. 45, Photocopies of holograph cello parts (Box-folder 27/6)
  - Sonata, cello and piano, op. 45, Photocopy of holograph full score; 35 p. [one of two] (Box-folder 27/7)
  - Sonata, cello and piano, op. 45, Photocopy of holograph full score; 35 p. [two of two] (Box-folder 27/8)
  - Sonata, cello and piano, op. 48a see also Sonata, violin and piano, op. 48, Holograph cello part (Movement II, Canzone) (Box-folder 36/11)
  - Sonata, cello and piano, op. 48a, Transparencies of holograph cello part (Box-folder 36/12)
  - Sonata, cello and piano, op. 48a, Photocopies of holograph cello part (Box-folder 36/13)
  - Sonata, piano, op. 28, B-flat minor, Holograph piano score; 44 p.; Original is classed in ML96.O53. (Box-folder 27/9)
  - Sonata, piano, op. 28, B-flat minor, Photocopy of printed edition; 39 p.; Chicago: Clayton F. Summy Co., 1910. (Box-folder 27/10)
  - Sonata, viola and piano, op. 45b, B-flat minor see also Sonata, cello and piano, op. 45, Transparencies of holograph viola parts (Box-folder 27/11)
  - Sonata, viola and piano, op. 45b, B-flat minor], Photocopies of holograph viola parts (Box-folder 27/12)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 48 see also Sonata, cello and piano, op. 48a, Photocopy of holograph piano-violin score, with annotations in pencil; 41 p. (Box-folder 36/1)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 48, Photocopy of holograph piano-violin score, with annotations in pencil; 41 p. (Box-folder 36/2)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 48, Photocopy of holograph piano-violin score; 41 p. (Box-folder 36/3)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 48, Holograph piano-violin score in black ink; 17 p., also p. 17a-32a (Box-folder 36/4)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 48, Holograph violin part (Box-folder 36/5)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 48, Transparencies of holograph piano-violin score; p. 2-41 (Box-folder 36/6)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 48, Transparencies of holograph violin part (Box-folder 36/7)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 48, Photocopies of holograph violin parts [one of two] (Box-folder 36/8)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 48, Photocopies of holograph violin parts [two of two] (Box-folder 36/9)
  - Sonata for violin, horn, and piano (arrangement of op. 48), Photocopy of holograph horn part (Box-folder 36/10)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 51, Photocopy of holograph piano-violin score; 29 p. (Box-folder 36/14)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 51, Photocopy of holograph piano-violin score; 29 p. (Box-folder 37/1)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 51, Holograph piano-violin score in black ink, with pasteovers, and annotations in pencil; 29 p. (Box-folder 37/2)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 51, Holograph violin part (Box-folder 37/3)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 51, Transparencies of holograph piano-violin score and holograph violin part (Box-folder 37/4)
  - Sonata, violin and piano, op. 51, Photocopies of holograph violin parts (Box-folder 37/5)
  - Sonatina, string orchestra, C major, Holograph full score; 25 p. (Box-folder 37/6)
  - Sonatina, string orchestra, C major, Holograph sketches in pencil; p. 13-14 (Box-folder 37/7)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Photocopy of holograph full score, with annotations in pencil and red pencil; 23 p. [one of five] (Box-folder 38/1)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Photocopy of holograph full score, with annotations in pencil and red pencil; 23 p. [two of five] (Box-folder 38/2)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Photocopy of holograph full score, with annotations in pencil and red pencil; 23 p. [three of five] (Box-folder 38/3)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Photocopy of holograph full score, with annotations in pencil and red pencil; 23 p. [four of five] (Box-folder 38/4)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Photocopy of holograph full score; 23 p. [five of five] (Box-folder 38/5)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Photocopies of holograph piano-vocal score (Box-folder 38/6)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Transparencies of holograph full score; p. 2-23 (Box-folder 38/7)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Transparencies of holograph piano-vocal [10 p.] and organ-vocal [p. 2-13] scores (Box-folder 38/8)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Holograph sketch for organ part, rehearsal 17, pencil; 1 p. (Box-folder 38/9)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Autograph cello part (Box-folder 38/10)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Transparencies of holograph string parts (Box-folder 38/11)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Transparencies of holograph woodwind, brass, and percussion parts (bassoon and trumpet parts wanting) (Box-folder 38/12)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Photocopies of holograph violin parts (Box-folder 39/1)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Photocopies of holograph viola, cello, and bass parts (Box-folder 39/2)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Photocopies of holograph flute and oboe parts (Box-folder 39/3)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Photocopies of holograph clarinet parts (Box-folder 39/4)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Photocopies of holograph bassoon and horn parts (Box-folder 39/5)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Photocopies of holograph trombone parts (Box-folder 39/6)
  - St. Francis of Assisi, Photocopies of holograph harp, celesta, and campanelle parts (Box-folder 39/7)
  - A study in relativity, Holograph full score; 14 p. (Box-folder 37/8)
  - A study in relativity, Holograph string parts (Box-folder 37/9)
  - A study in relativity, Holograph woodwind, brass, and percussion parts (Box-folder 37/10)
  - Symphonic concerto, cello and orchestra, Holograph full score, 232 p. (Box-folder 40/1)